A journey, in search of home.
The Boy, the Mole, the Fox and the Horse is a animation,
family, adventure film directed by Charlie Mackesy.
The unlikely friendship of a boy, a mole, a fox and a horse
traveling together in the boy's search for home.
The Boy (voice), played by Jude Coward Nicoll.
The Mole (voice), played by Tom Hollander.
The Fox (voice), played by Idris Elba.
The Horse (voice), played by Gabriel Byrne.
The Boy, the Mole, the Fox and the Horse is a 2019
illustrated book by Charlie Mackesy.
It follows the developing friendship between the four titular protagonists, this is continued in the
sequel: Always Remember: The Boy, the Mole, the Fox, the Horse and the Storm (2025).
The film explores themes of friendship, hope, fox,
horse, based on children's book.
The tone is uplifting.